Neugass, Fritz; Papers ger007
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Articles with text and photos by Neugass, 1950s-1979; 9; 60 file folders
  - Columns, Castles, Minarets. Ca. 100 photos from Fritz Neugass' trips in the Mediterranean, most with captions, Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 36)
  - Coney Island. Texts in German and English, with captions but no photos (preserved separately), Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 37)
  - County Fairs in the US. Texts and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (86), clipping, Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 38)
  - Debutante Ball, Astor Hotel, New York, 1958 (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 39)
    Text in German, photographs by Neugass (11), program, guest lists, press release.
  - Enterprising spirit of an American boy (Jackie O'Neill). Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (10), Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 40)
  - Gambling in America, Reno, NV, etc. Text and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (20), clippings, Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 41)
  - George Washington statue on Wall Street. Text in German and English, photographs by Neugass (4), Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 42)
  - The George Washington Bridge. Text in English, photographs by Neugass (5), Undated (Box 23 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 43)
  - German Embassy, Washington, DC, 1955 (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 1)
    Text in German, photographs by Neugass (15), negatives, contact prints, press releases, clipping.
  - Ghost-town, Virginia City, NV. Text in German, photographs by Neugass (21) with negatives and contact prints, clipping, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 2)
  - Greenwich Village, artistic boheme life in New York. Text and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (37), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 3)
  - Gypsy pilgrimage in Saintes Maries-de-la-Mer. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (18), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 4)
  - Hollywood Cemetery. Text in German, photographs by Neugass (17) with negatives and contact prints, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 5)
  - Hymn to an egg-slicer. Text and captions in English, photograph by Neugass, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 6)
  - In a helicopter above New York. Texts in German and English, photographs by Neugass (29) with contact prints, press releases, clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 7)
  - Indians in the USA. Texts (3) and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (53), press releases, clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 8)
  - Italians in New York, including San Genaro procession. Texts and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (35), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 9)
  - Jalayer, Freidoon, Persian employee at the American Museum of Natural History. Text and captions in German, contact prints, photographs by Neugass (2), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 10)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, meeting in New York Stadium, 1953 July (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 11)
    Text in German and English, photographs by Neugass (11), with contact prints.
  - Lall, Shusheila, wife of Indian diplomat Arthur Lall in New York. Text in German, photographs by Neugass (6), clipping, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 12)
  - Life Begins at Forty. Forty Plus Club, New York. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (11), with contact prints, clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 13)
  - Lindt, August, U.N. High Commissioner for Refugees, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 14)
    Texts by Fritz Neugass and Edith Gloor, a Swiss journalist, photographs by Neugass (4).
  - Lunch concert in Bryant Park. Texts in German and English, photographs by Neugass (12), clipping, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 15)
  - Mexico. Texts (5) in German and English with captions, but without photos (preserved separately), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 16)
  - Model photos, series of (5) photos by Neugass of a girl in Central Park. Text in English, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 17)
  - Mount Athos. Text and captions in English, photographs by Neugass (17), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 18)
  - Museum of Modern Art Sculpture Garden. Text in German, photographs by Neugass (24), with contact prints, press release, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 19)
  - New Orleans, Poetry exhibit. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (6), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 20)
  - New York City. Texts (9) and captions in German and in English, no photos (preserved separately), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 21)
  - New York's architectural styles. Text in English, photographs by Neugass (28), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 22)
  - New York City seen through arches. Text and captions in English, photographs by Neugass (14), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 23)
  - Oberkirchen Children's chorus in New York, 1955 (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 24)
    Texts (3) and captions in English and German, contact prints, photographs by Neugass (29), publicity photos (4), press releases.
  - Passion Play in Roquebrune, France. Texts (2) and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (19), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 25)
  - Photographic methods. Texts (7) in English and German, no photographs (preserved separately), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 26)
  - Photographing Monuments (New York City). Text and captions in English, photographs by Neugass (34), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 27)
  - Play streets in New York. Text and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (23), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 28)
  - Provincetown, Cape Cod. Captions in English, no text, photographs by Neugass (52), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 29)
  - Provincetown, setting out at night with fishermen. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (15), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 30)
  - Provincetown Playhouse. Text in German, captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (19), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 31)
  - Reflections. Texts (8) and captions in German and English, original photos by Fritz Neugass (46), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 32)
  - Sailors Snug Harbor, retirement home for sailors. Text and captions in German, photographs by Neugass (20), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 33)
  - Swimming University, Council on Student Travel. Texts and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (37), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 34)
  - Terramycin in the breeding of pigs. Texts in German and French, with contact prints, photographs by Neugass (17), clippings, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 35)
  - Tinos Island (Greece) Pilgrimage. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (13), Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 36)
  - Volunteer Service Photographers, Rehabilitation through Photography. Text and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (30), pamphlet, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 37)
  - Window-Display in the US. Texts and captions in German and English, photographs by Neugass (47), clipping, Undated (Box 24 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 38)
  - Afrikanische Kunst / African Art. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 1)
    See also Series I, Box 1, Folder 4.
  - Afro-amerikanische Kunst / Afro-American Art, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 2)
    See also Series I, Box 1, Folder 5.
  - Corot, Jean-Baptiste-Camille. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 3)
    See also Series I, Box 2, Folder 23.
  - Ernst, Max. Oversize photo, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 4)
    See also Series I, Box 3, Folder 9.
  - Feininger, Andreas. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 5)
    See also Series I, Box 3, Folder 16.
  - Jaki Horvat Joze. Correspondence between Neugass and Karl Berndt concerning Yugoslavian surrealist painter, Jaki, 1965-1969 (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 6)
    Photographs (50), also several hundred small format photographs (3" x 5"), boxed separately.
  - Jaki Horvat Joze. Printed materials, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 7)
  - Jaki Horvat Joze. Catalogs, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 8)
  - Monet, Claude. Oversize photo, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 9)
    See also Series I, Box 5, Folder 30.
  - Picasso, Pablo. Printed materials, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 10)
    See also Series I, Box 6, Folder 14.
  - Renoir, Pierre Auguste, Undated; Oversize photos (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 11)
    See also Series I, Box 7, Folder 9.
  - Christie's 200-year celebration. Printed materials, notes, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 12)
    See also Series III, Box 15, Folder 53.
  - Antiquarian Books: Zeitlin & Ver Brugge. Catalog, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 13)
    See also Series III, Box 16, Folder 31.
  - Art dealers in Europe. Catalog, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 14)
    See also Series III, Box 16, Folder 26.
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd. Printed materials, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 15)
    See also Series IV, Box 18, Folder 30.
  - American Photographs, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 16)
    Oversize photo.
    See also Series VII, Box 20, Folder 18.
  - Avedon, Richard. Catalog, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 17)
    See also Series VII, Box 20, Folder 21.
  - Cartier-Bresson, Henri. Oversize photo, printed materials, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 18)
    See also Series VII, Box 20, Folder 31.
  - Industrial Photography. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 19)
    See also Series VII, Box 21, Folder 10.
  - Japan. Photography in Japan Today. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 20)
    See also Series VII, Box 21, Folder 13.
  - Läubli, Walter. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 21)
    See also Series VII, Box 21, Folder 16.
  - Larsen, Lisa. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 22)
    See also Series VII, Box 21, Folder 20.
  - Museum of Modern Art. Photo-Exhibits, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 23)
    See also Series VII, Box 21, Folder 27.
  - Weegee. Oversize photos, Undated (Box 25 (9-Articles with text and photos by ), Folder 24)
    See also Series VII, Box 22, Folder 6.
- Published Writings by Fritz Neugass (clippings), 1942-1979; 10; 186 file folders
  This series consists of newspaper and magazine clippings of articles by Fritz Neugass in German, English, French and Dutch. Approximately 3000 clippings have been arranged by subjects: art, museums & collections, art market, architecture, furniture & design, theater & film, photography, general journalistic articles, photojournalism and books and manuscripts. Many of the clippings are reprints or translations of the same article. There is also a separate series of ca. 220 articles, which appeared in the German Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1964-1979.
  Arranged by subject and chronologically within subject category.
  - Art, 1948; 1 item (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 1)
  - Art, 1949; 4 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 2)
  - Art, 1950; 3 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 3)
  - Art, 1951; 6 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 4)
  - Art, 1952; 8 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 5)
  - Art, 1953; 13 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 6)
  - Art, 1954; 9 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 7)
  - Art, 1955; 28 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 8)
  - Art, 1956; 29 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 9)
  - Art, 1957; 20 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 10)
  - Art, 1958; 22 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 11)
  - Art, 1959; 18 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 12)
  - Art, 1960; 42 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 13)
  - Art, 1961; 28 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 14)
  - Art, 1962; 19 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 15)
  - Art, 1963; 30 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 16)
  - Art, 1964; 23 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 17)
  - Art, 1965; 45 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 18)
  - Art, 1966; 63 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 19)
  - Art, 1967; 40 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 20)
  - Art, 1968; 29 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 21)
  - Art, 1969; 34 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 22)
  - Art, 1970; 20 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 23)
  - Art, 1971; 11 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 24)
  - Art, 1972; 17 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 25)
  - Art, 1973; 20 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 26)
  - Art, 1974; 7 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 27)
  - Art, 1975; 13 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 28)
  - Art, 1976; 8 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 29)
  - Art, 1977; 16 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 30)
  - Art, 1978; 17 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 31)
  - Art, 1979; 7 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 32)
  - Museums and Collections, 1951; 7 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 33)
  - Museums and Collections, 1952; 8 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 34)
  - Museums and Collections, 1953; 4 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 35)
  - Museums and Collections, 1954; 6 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 36)
  - Museums and Collections, 1955; 11 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 37)
  - Museums and Collections, 1956; 3 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 38)
  - Museums and Collections, 1957; 11 items (Box 26 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 39)
  - Museums and Collections, 1958; 11 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 1)
  - Museums and Collections, 1959; 13 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 2)
  - Museums and Collections, 1960; 11 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 3)
  - Museums and Collections, 1961; 5 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 4)
  - Museums and Collections, 1962; 7 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 5)
  - Museums and Collections, 1963; 19 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 6)
  - Museums and Collections, 1964; 18 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 7)
  - Museums and Collections, 1965; 30 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 8)
  - Museums and Collections, 1966; 26 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 9)
  - Museums and Collections, 1967; 9 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 10)
  - Museums and Collections, 1968; 17 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 11)
  - Museums and Collections, 1969; 18 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 12)
  - Museums and Collections, 1970; 12 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 13)
  - Museums and Collections, 1971; 20 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 14)
  - Museums and Collections, 1972; 18 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 15)
  - Museums and Collections, 1973; 14 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 16)
  - Museums and Collections, 1974; 12 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 17)
  - Museums and Collections, 1975; 10 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 18)
  - Museums and Collections, 1976; 7 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 19)
  - Museums and Collections, 1977; 4 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 20)
  - Museums and Collections, 1978; 12 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 21)
  - Art Market, 1950-1951; 6 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 22)
  - Art Market, 1952-1954; 11 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 23)
  - Art Market, 1955-1956; 12 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 24)
  - Art Market, 1957-1958; 15 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 25)
  - Art Market, 1959; 31 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 26)
  - Art Market, 1960; 45 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 27)
  - Art Market, 1961; 41 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 28)
  - Art Market, 1962; 48 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 29)
  - Art Market, 1963; 50 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 30)
  - Art Marker, 1964; 52 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 31)
  - Art Market, 1965; 51 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 32)
  - Art Market, 1966; 47 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 33)
  - Art Market, 1967; 40 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 34)
  - Art Market, 1968; 24 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 35)
  - Art Market, 1969; 31 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 36)
  - Art Market, 1970; 29 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 37)
  - Art Market, 1971; 29 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 38)
  - Art Market, 1972; 36 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 39)
  - Art Market, 1973; 38 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 40)
  - Art Market, 1974; 36 items (Box 27 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 41)
  - Art Market, 1975; 28 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 1)
  - Art Market, 1976; 41 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 2)
  - Art Market, 1977; 27 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 3)
  - Art Market, 1978; 28 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 4)
  - Art Market, 1979; 14 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 5)
  - Architecture, 1950; 4 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 6)
  - Architecture, 1951; 5 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 7)
  - Architecture, 1952; 7 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 8)
  - Architecture, 1953-1954; 6 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 9)
  - Architecture, 1955; 12 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 10)
  - Architecture, 1956; 11 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 11)
  - Architecture, 1957; 11 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 12)
  - Architecture, 1958; 8 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 13)
  - Architecture, 1959; 15 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 14)
  - Architecture, 1960; 8 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 15)
  - Architecture, 1961-1962; 7 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 16)
  - Architecture, 1963-1964; 16 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 17)
  - Architecture, 1965; 18 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 18)
  - Architecture, 1966; 19 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 19)
  - Architecture, 1967-1968; 5 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 20)
  - Furniture & Design, 1950-1951; 10 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 21)
  - Furniture & Design, 1952-1954; 10 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 22)
  - Furniture & Design, 1955-1956; 11 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 23)
  - Furniture & Design, 1957-1958; 9 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 24)
  - Furniture & Design, 1959-1960; 9 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 25)
  - Furniture & Design, 1961-1964; 6 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 26)
  - Furniture & Design, 1965; 13 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 27)
  - Furniture & Design, 1966; 19 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 28)
  - Furniture & Design, 1967-1968; 5 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 29)
  - Theater & Film, 1953-1954; 5 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 30)
  - Theater & Film, 1955; 14 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 31)
  - Theater & Film, 1956; 11 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 32)
  - Theater & Film, 1957; 13 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 33)
  - Theater & Film, 1958-1975; 21 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 34)
  - Photography, 1948-1950; 13 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 35)
  - Photography, 1951; 14 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 36)